I wonder if the customer will say anything?
お客さんが何か言ってくれるかな?
Like.
みたいな
What should I do?
どうしようかな?
What is it called?
何て言う名前になってるんだっけ?
Maya!
マヤ!
It's kind of eye-catching.
なんか、動眼だよね
lie?
嘘?
TRUE?
本当?
Isn't that so?
そうでもないか
Beautiful face.
美人顔
Beautiful face?
美人顔?
I guess it's a moving eye.
なんか、動眼じゃないかな
Her eyes are beautiful.
目が綺麗です
Somehow, people say that I have a moving eye,
なんか、人に動眼だねって言われたり、
Because people say I'm sloppy,
雑っぽいねって言われたりするから、
I don't know.
分かんない
Depending on how you look at it, it may seem quite adult-like.
見方によっては、結構大人っぽいかもしれない
The eyes aren't dark.
目、くっくりではないじゃん
It's a little refreshing.
ちょっとシュッとしてる
Beautiful type.
綺麗系
But since it's thin, it might look a little like this.
でも、細いから、ちょっとこのっぽく見えるかもしれないね
Because it's small.
小さいから
It's white.
白いよね
It's definitely white.
絶対白いよ
TRUE?
本当?
Yeah.
うん
You'll be told.
言われるっしょ
People say it's white.
白いねって言われる
When did you last have fun?
最近いつイッチした?
About a week ago.
一週間前とか
How do you usually live?
いつもどんな感じで住むの?
How do you usually feel?
いつもどんな感じで?
Normally.
普通に
Just tell me.
普通教えてよ
Ordinary.
普通の
What is normal?
普通にって何?
What is it?
何だろう?
We went to bed normally, and how are we getting along?
普通にベッド入って、そっから仲は?
Like.
みたいな
I don't understand, sister.
お姉ちゃん分かんない
what?
何?
Do you want to chew?
チューすんの?
Depends on the person.
その人による
Ah, some people don't chew.
あっ、チューしない人もいる
Well, that's true.
まあそうだよね
I wouldn't try it if it wasn't cute.
俺、可愛くなかったらチューしないわ
That's right.
そうなんだ
If I don't like it, I won't chew it.
好みじゃなかったら俺はチューしないから
Oh yeah.
あーね
I don't know.
分かんない
Some people may not like chews.
チュー好きじゃない人もいるかもね
Yeah.
うん
What should I do?
どうしようかな
Then, can I have you stand for once?
じゃあ一回立ってもらってもいい?
Is this okay?
ここでいい?
Okay.
いいよ
She's really beautiful, really.
めっちゃ美人ですよ、ほんと
Turn a little to the left.
ちょっと左向いて
I won't be photographed.
撮られたりしないよ
cute.
可愛 い
Your hair is definitely thin.
絶対毛薄いよね
I don't know.
分かんない
I guess it's normal.
普通かな
I think it's normal.
普通だと思う
cold?
寒い?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Okay, then turn this way.
いいよ、じゃあこっち向いて
Will you please sit down?
座ってくれる?
By the way, is there anything that feels good?
ちなみにどこが気持ちいいとかあります?
Where does it feel good?
どこが気持ちいい?
Especially?
別に?
What do you think?
どうだろう?
middle?
中?
I like what's inside.
中が好きなんだ
But I don't like fingers.
けど、指は好きじゃない
Do you like to put it in?
入れるのが好き?
Why can't it be bigger than your finger?
なんで指よりでけえじゃん
I can tell people that my finger hurts.
指は人に言えるけど痛い
nail?
爪?
Maybe you didn't cut your nails.
爪切ってなかったりとか
It's better to meet normally than with fingers.
指より普通に出会えたほうがいい
Is it pretty easy to get to?
結構行きやすい?
I won't go at all.
全然行かない
Have you ever been there?
行ったことある?
I've never been there.
行ったことない
Seriously?
マジで?
Have you never been?
行ったことないの?
do not have.
ない
I wish I had brought something today.
今日何か持ってくればよかった
I was on my way home from work.
仕事帰りだったから
That?
あれを?
Have you ever used a telephone?
電話とか使ったことある?
I've used the phone before.
電話は使ったことある
Ah, I've been to Chestnut.
あ、栗で行ったことある
You can't go with chestnuts.
栗では行けない
It's not because I'm young.
若いからじゃない
Okay.
いいよ
erase?
消す?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
It's really good.
めっちゃいい
It's okay to fall asleep.
寝ちゃっていいよ
beautiful.
綺麗
cute.
かわいい
nice.
いいね
It won't disappear.
消えない
Can you open it yourself?
自分で開ける?
Either is fine.
どっちでもいいよ
Why don't you do something?
何とかしないの?
What not?
何しない
Is that it?
あれなのかな?
No sexual desire?
性欲ない?
Not really.
そんなない
Maybe it's not easy to understand.
わかりやすくないのかもね
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
I don't know.
わかんない
It doesn't matter how I feel.
どこ感じるとかまんまないんだ
What about your chest?
胸はどうなの?
usually.
普通
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
Is that so?
そうかな?
Not told?
言われない?
My chest feels good.
胸気持ちよさそう
I feel like that.
なんかそんな気がする
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
It definitely feels good, let me tell you this.
絶対気持ちいいじゃん、これ言ったら
Will it be said?
言 われる?
It feels good.
気持ちいいって
It's very narrow.
めっちゃ狭い
I can't really paint it, though.
あんま塗れないね、でも
I wanted to take it wherever I went.
行くとこ取りたかった
Did you think you could go?
行けそうだった?
subtle?
微妙?
I don't know.
わかんない
How can I go?
どうしたら行くとかあるの?
I think I'll go if this happens.
これされたら行くみたいな
When did you go?
いつ行ったの?
I can't go unless I use my phone.
電話使わないと行かないんだ
There are no people who don't use their phones to go there.
電話使って行かない人もいないよね
May I touch you for a moment?
ちょっと触ってもらおうかな
cute.
かわいい
Maybe I should read it again.
また読んじゃおうかな
Please come and see us.
ぜひぜひ
I really like it.
僕はめっちゃ好き
Type wise.
タイプ割と
If it's not cute, it's extravagant.
かわいくないと、贅沢でしょ
I'm cute.
自分かわいい
It's delicious.
うまいね
Who did you learn from?
誰に習ったの?
You're really good at it.
めっちゃ上手じゃん
TRUE?
本当?
I won't be able to take it.
取れなくなっちゃう
You can get on top.
上 乗ってもらえるじゃん
put in?
入れる?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
It's tight so it's okay.
きついから大丈夫
I said it's okay if I go up.
上がったらいいって
Isn't it too tight?
きつくない?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Which type do you like?
どのタイプが好き?
Like on the battlefield.
戦場に好き
It's okay if you're tired.
疲れたらいいよ
Shall we go down?
下になろうか
I haven't gotten much.
あんまり取れてない
Does your hand hurt?
手が痛い?
Shiromukeru?
しろむける?
Can you look at me?
こ っち見てくれる?
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
cute.
かわいい
There is a washroom, a bath and toiletries,
洗面所があって、お風呂とトイレ物で、
There is a proper room and a bedroom,
ちゃん と部屋がリミングと寝室があって、
The room was nice.
っていう 部屋がよかった
I wanted a house that felt like a proper home,
ちゃんと家っていう感じの家がよかったから、
I lived there, but it was expensive.
そこに住んだんだけどさ、高いよね
Shinjuku is expensive.
新宿は高いよ
But, where I live, it's fine.
でもね、私が住んでるところ、ちあんいい
Which side?
どの辺?
Do you know where the vacant space is?
空き場の場所わかる?
Is it the Shinjuku line?
新宿線の方か
Isn't it around Shinjuku?
新宿周辺じゃないの?
It's a short walk if you take a taxi, but it's too far to walk home.
タクシーだとすぐなんだけど、 歩いては帰れない距離
But it's just a taxi away, and Kabuki is right there.
でもタクシーすぐだし、 歌舞伎すぐこれだし、
But it's so nice that it's quite comfortable to live in.
でもちあんいいから、 結構住みやすい
Even in Wakeboro Bridge, more than 100,000 people lived there.
わけぼろ橋でも10万以上住んだね
Do, do, do.
するするする
It's close to 1 anyway.
どうせ1から近いんでしまう
It's a bit of a walk, Marshon.
ちょっと歩くけど、 マーション、
That's cute.
その、かわいいね
I bought it because it was cute, but it's an off-shoulder aircraft.
かわいいから買ったんだけどさ、 オフショル機体で、
If you raise your hand, it will come right back.
手をパッとあげると、 すぐ戻っちゃうの
The width of your shoulders is nice.
肩幅いいよね
I may sound like a maniac, but I don't really like anything beyond shoulder 5.
マニアックなこと言うけど、 あんまり肩5つ以降好きじゃない
Can't I get 5?
私5つくない?
Because I played volleyball. Did you play volleyball?
バレーやってたからさ、 バレーやってたの?
So what can you do?
じゃあ何かできるの?
Because volleyball is volleyball.
バ レーってバレーボールだからね
That volleyball?
そっちのバレー?
I don't think so.
別に思わないよ
Your head is small, isn't it?
頭 ちっちゃいよね
It's like a mirror.
鏡みたいになってる
This is a new one.
これ新しいやつだよ
I'm still six.
私まだシックスだよ
No, buy it.
いや、買えよ
If you live in a place where prices are that high, you should buy it.
そんなに価値高いところ住んでたら買えよ
I can buy it next time.
今度買える
I want to buy it soon.
そろそろ買えたい
I want to lend you a line.
ライン貸したい
Can I sit separately?
別に座っていい?
You don't have to squat down there.
そんなとこにしゃがまなくても
I'll take your pants.
パンツ取るぞ
That's cute.
それかわいい
It's a pain to take it from here.
ここから取るとめんどくさいよ
It's okay to take it slow,
別にゆっくりしていってもいいし、
You can go home, it doesn't matter.
帰ってもいいし、どっちでもいいよ
You can watch TV.
テレビ見ていってもいいし
Shall I smoke a cigarette and go home for a while?
たばこ吸ってちょっとしたら帰るのかな?
Understood.
わかった